{
    "id": "b63ddd42e0a0498b9d3ed4b29278652d",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She was anxious ……………………………… her husband hadn’t returned yet.",
            "description": "Because gives the reason for something.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "52c762f9adc2459eae2321f644c23afa"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… you miss another deadline, you will be sacked.",
            "description": "If expresses a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e55e68b6792c48e199ccb9e828c15908"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… he is old, he cannot walk properly.",
            "description": "As gives the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "Like"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "79f8fbfa795446dfbeaa7ebab4100185"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is neither kind …………………………. friendly.",
            "description": "Note the pattern neither...nor...",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "and",
                "nor"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6a979fe0d4c7456eb1b9b4592f9c276c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will not permit this …………………………… it is against my principles.",
            "description": "Because indicates the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "hence",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "26cbc3fa8f92481b8dd5574e05d7d683"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can go ……………………………. you have finished that report.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "after",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0a10025d353f4818b26a881d35cadb55"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. you are not feeling well, I will take you to the doctor.",
            "description": "If expresses a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Until",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2ddf1cb56b254e5ca8018022292c685f"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………………… I pleaded for help, he didn’t move.",
            "description": "Even though is used to emphasize a contrast.",
            "answers": [
                "Even if",
                "Even though",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9411d07233d546a0b431cb2882f08313"
        },
        {
            "question": "She worked ................................... hard that her health deteriorated.",
            "description": "We use so before an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fa5b1724c4ba46d2ad56d8ddc6d21feb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The faster you run, ……………………………. you get tired.",
            "description": "The comparative is used in both clauses in this structure. ",
            "answers": [
                "sooner",
                "the sooner",
                "the soon"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cec9f0ad00e440deb1b3853a792aaf94"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. he was the most popular candidate, he got eliminated in the first round itself.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Since",
                "As"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ec61b4f845544d1093e80ac54d365823"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the store ………………………….. they sell fish.",
            "description": "Where means in which.",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "05db062347c64ba88b127ec1abb0843a"
        }
    ]
}